welcome to the stoa
the stoa is a digital campfire where we
cohere
and dialogue about what matters most at
the knife's edge
of what's happening now
all right check-ins uh well go first you
want me to go first
uh i'll go i feel
i feel mostly light in my body there's a
little alarm going off
i feel uh yeah quite light and sort of
uh
a giddiness that came up in the stowa
session the other day the use of the
word giddiness
and uh yeah i feel
excited to be here with you peter
[Music]
so i i feel a wave of warmth just
hearing that
uh your last share um there's like sort
of like a
like a really solid groundedness i feel
right now
and there's uh maybe like 0.5
nervousness um it's not a lot of coffee
today so that could be
that might have something to do with it
cool
so yeah
i guess to set some context for people
who are uh just tuning in like
who the heck are these guys what are
they talking about with their check-ins
um so people who have been coming to the
store are regular users and people who
are actually facilitators here
i am um inviting them on my podcast
essentially
and this is going to be on youtube but
eventually it's going to be on the
actual podcast
uh and it serves two purposes really
just like an
opportunity to get to know you more
because
we talked in in store sessions we
chatted for like 30 minutes on practical
stuff
we were texting each other sending each
other like freestyle raps
but we never actually have like a good
proper chat
you know so it's like so it's like what
that's an opportunity which which
which i i'm looking forward to and the
other one is to introduce you
to the already established audience that
i have on the podcast and the youtube
channel and whatnot
so then they get they can get attracted
to what you're bringing to the store
so i guess like um maybe it's like a
high level question like
who are you tyson
and you can take that in any direction
yeah thank you for asking
i i mean i am
deeply fascinated and interested in
freestyle
and what that is to me is creative
self-expression
and what creative self-expression is to
me is like is it
engagement in what is emerging it's
engaging it's participating
in what is happening right now and
i think there's something that it's like
there's a signal that i send
to the uh the world the universe
the cosmos there's a signal that i send
when i start
wanting to share the experience of
creative self-expression with others
like if i choose to sort of embody
a facilitator role or a teacher role or
just a like a sharing
and there's something about that that
really amplifies
my experience of that participation in
creativity and so i mean
i'm who i'm i feel like a conduit at
times for
freestyle i feel like a conduit for
spontaneous
in the moment self-expression and i
think the reason that i feel
so resonant with being that is because
of how much time i spent in my life in
the past
overthinking and being like stifled
um experiencing that paralysis by
analysis
being so caught up in rehearsing
the things that i did whether it was
talking to a woman i was attracted to
or it was approaching someone that i saw
as a mentor or a teacher a guide and i
wanted to
get to know them or i mean
so many things the list goes on and on
and so
i am really in the the discovery of
how can i live more in
flow and in full participation in my
whole
body and um and then i think i guess
the part of the part of this this hero's
journey is to then want to
share the things that i've learned with
other people like guys try this on it's
really fun
yeah and so just to pay you a compliment
i really like your voice
you know the sound of your voice the
quality of it there's like a there's
like a
masculinity to it there's like there's
like a youthfulness to it
and like an earnestness to it so you got
a lot of good stuff going on there
i i want to make you blush and giggle up
before the the show's over
um so yeah so you do a session
at the stoa every saturday 8pm eastern
time called freestyling uh through a
pandemic or during a pandemic i can't
remember we're probably going to rename
it
a little bit um yeah so how did you get
into freestyling before we talk about
the actual session how did you get into
it
cool thank you so i was without giving
the whole backstory i found myself
in hawaii on this beautiful property
this piece of land
like right next to where a lot of the
filming for jurassic park was done and i
was there
participating in a retreat that i helped
organize
um so there were some influential like
social media
celebs and some of the american ninja
warriors
and some musicians like this eclectic
group of people that were sort of
invited
to come and participate in this social
experiment called tribe design
seeing how strong of a tribe these
people could
form all meeting each other for the
first time but then there was also that
twist of like inviting people that
had followings so that they could market
it so it was this combination of
a social experiment and this and like a
business project
and but at the pillar of the they're at
the
let's see the foundation of the
experience was engaging in experiments
around self-acceptance to
self-expression
and radical authenticity those are sort
of our nodes
and we invited to musicians
so tubby love and the roots family for
anyone that's listening is looking for
his like good
soulful hawaiian like rootsy music
and other musicians dustin thomas he's
amazing
and so you could say these these these
are musicians that have been inspired by
like xavier rudd trevor hall if anyone's
heard of those artists
anyway they would just break out in
musical jam sessions like in the kitchen
outside you just be walking all of a
sudden you hear someone's beatboxing and
someone else walks up with their guitar
and starts playing along and then
as a girl walks up and starts singing
and then someone will step in and start
freestyling
and i was so amazed to see these
people that could just like turn on like
that in them i don't know it's like it
seemed like at a moment's notice
and because it seems so far from what i
had experienced and i also grew up
thinking i had no musical gifts
whatsoever
so one thing led to another and we did
actually like a full
freestyle circle this was a formal
exercise in this retreat experience
where everyone was going to get in the
center of the circle and freestyle
whether they have any experience or not
and i waited till like right till the
very end until someone was like pushing
me in like it's your turn get in there
and i went in freestyled probably just
you know i had a blacked out
i don't remember a thing that i said and
that was it
but i just remember this sense being
with me that like
keep practicing that like that was so
hard for me
but simultaneously like so exciting
it was that balance of this is
impossible
and i really want to be able to do it
and so then i was lucky enough to have a
really good friend
that i spent some time with in san diego
and he played guitar and he's saying
and so in the evenings we kind of just
like sit around um
on a park bench or something looking up
at the stars and he'd play guitar and
we'd just take turns going back and
forth
i'm just freestyling and then that's
when it kind of that's when it caught me
and when you mean caught you like um did
you join like groups clubs you practice
every day like what does that look like
yeah so i did at this time i was just
very compelled towards doing things to
risk my reputation
very influenced by brad blanton and
radical honesty
and so any opportunity i had to like
risk my reputation i was looking for it
and so i went live on facebook um
for an extended number of days in a row
every day while i was hanging out with
my friend we would go live on facebook
and freestyle and just like film each
other
play beats and in these videos i'm like
pale
i'm already quite white but i am just as
white as can be just ghost white
you can see my voice in my face it's
like sort of trembling
and so what it caught me was this like
this opportunity to sort of shed the
skin of who i'm not like i could see
myself
and the tension that was in my body as i
was doing this and how hard it was and i
wanted to just like
i wanted to break through that whatever
that hard layer was
that kept me from just being fluid and
free in my expression
and so it was that it was and then it
was
also the fact that i was doing this with
a friend we were kind of sharing in this
practice together and there was this
shared struggle and so
there was this um every day this
accountability we would like wake up and
just play beats and start freestyling
and so there was something about the way
that it connected the two of us
if it was if it weren't for that if i
was in my room alone doing this
right there would have been no hope like
no chance that i would have loved it the
way that i did
it was the way that it connected the two
of us that
um was important to it like i said like
catching me like i just couldn't stop
yeah and how long ago was that when you
first went to that conference or that
festival
and then until now yeah that was uh
about four years ago
and then since then it's kind of it's
coming waves into my life
freestyle yeah yeah yeah yeah i asked
that question just because you're
pretty good at it from my perspective
because i wonder how long that journey
was
and so you you how did you get on the
radar star's radar again you
you've the game b space is that yeah
yeah so i've been
yeah i've been paying attention to
jordan hall daniel schmuckenberger john
vavaki and so at some point
maybe like you uploaded a video of john
or something and it was
recommended youtube right something like
that
cool cool yeah so i i started seeing you
come at the quest
uh the slow sessions asking great
questions
very eager i forget how yeah you emailed
me something i even know how we
initially
encountered well and i would talk i
mentioned freestyle in a session
and then someone else sent me a message
on zoom and they were like
i've been thinking about using freestyle
it's a tool for sense making
and then since then he and i have
freestyled a lot together in these
virtual sessions so but i like
it the meeting closed before i could get
his contact info so then i reached out
to you asking for it and that kind of i
think opened
some of the possibilities yeah i was
running a full damon energy so i was
like oh something's there i could sniff
something out right
and then i think you and i talked and
i'm like let's do it let's do a
freestyling sense making freestyling
session i really love the idea
um well then i had reached out to you as
well like wanting to support the stoa
with sort of like administrative duties
because that's what a lot of what i've
done in the past like this retreat for
example what got me to that retreat
with some people that i had been
following on youtube and tracking and
were role models to me i reached out to
them i helped them with logistics
so that's been like this sort of this
tools like how i would get into circles
that i wanted to involve myself
in was with administrative duties and
logistics so
i went kind of back onto that um
that pattern and that's the essence that
i reached out to you in
but you were so quick to call out that
freestyle energy and just like
didn't even give much attention to the
whole logistics thing
right and so i appreciate you for that
that was
like quite refreshing and it felt good
to be like seen in that way you were
like it's like you wanted
my best gift and only that everything
else was like
let's leave that let's not mess with
that for now yeah yeah yeah yeah
you know like who knows like you might
you're helping out the store in
many capacities but yeah right there
that moment it's like
i want you to give i want i want to give
his gift to the world and uh or at least
a good part of it and this seems like it
this is freestyling stuff um
and so we kind of workshop briefly you
did most of it obviously
and now we have the session every week
at the stoa um
freestyling through a pandemic again
we're probably going to rename it but
uh i i did i was at the first one or the
second one and i'm like wow
i was at my knife's edge man like you
know like
before i tell a little bit more of my
experience like maybe you can kind of
like generally
to people what's it like doing a
freestyling pandemic with tyson
nice yeah to me it's an intentional
space
to practice leaning into
uncertainty and unknowingness and so
some of the sessions we even started by
just popcorning in and sharing just
speaking what's something that you're
deeply in the process is a process of or
what is something that's uncertain
unknown for you especially right now and
then we go into the freestyle
as if that is a practice and becoming
more intimate with
not knowing because that's sort of the
nature of freestyle and streaming our
consciousness is that
we don't know what we're gonna say so
you have the opportunity i think to feel
like it's a very approachable space to
step into that unknown creative
self-expression and really have a group
of people like hyping you up as you do
it
that's something that i really wanted to
be known for is like when i'm
freestyling i can look at the grid view
and i just see all these smiley faces
and people waving their hands
and that to me whatever energy comes up
whether it's
sometimes when i'm just freestyling like
things will come up that seem like
like dark thoughts or negativity or
things will come up where i just seem
like i'm confused and lost and i don't
know what i'm talking about or sometimes
i think that i sound like really
impressive and awesome that's the whole
spectrum
but it's it's an opportunity to just
embrace that
and let what comes up come out and then
be like really celebrated for that
yeah yeah that's good that's that's the
feeling uh when we did it
when i did it the first time it's like
first of all there's this group flow
like you're just like
there's i think 10 people everyone's
just flowing together with the beat
and you know like people are messing up
pausing you know feeling stupid and
everyone's just shining love on them
and when i went up it was like in my
head you know just like i'm creating
when listening to the people it's like
creating lines in my head like i'm going
to say this i'm going to say this i'm
going to say this like it's like i
because
i have acting background and so it's
like you're all memorizing lines and
stuff like that
and uh when i used to public speak i
used to memorize my speech verbatim
right and then just i was good at
memorizing but
you need to be extemporaneous if you're
going to be really like a live speaker
that people want to watch
watch watch you speak and the same thing
with freestyle and then the way you're
presenting it you can't have
something prepared uh or maybe you can
you kind of arrange it like those rap
battlers do but
if you go in without getting a script of
how it's gonna come out it's gonna
you're gonna look stupid or you're gonna
it's just gonna
not gonna land um you just gotta like
let it flow
and then when you let it flow like when
i let it flow it's like i didn't think i
was that good but at least
i leaned into it and if something came
out of my mouth and i got love
on that behalf on behalf of everyone
else and just felt really really really
good
yeah i hear that so like i think that
there's this is so interesting the way i
connect to us with this process of
thinking in public and wanting to share
the process
because i too all the time i
i mean i have things that i've written i
have things that i can lean on and it's
tempting
because it gives me that certainty of
like well people might
begin to identify me as the things that
i say here
and so it's safe to go back to the
things that i've written in the past
that i've chosen is like this is a good
representation of me
and what i believe and who i am let me
express that
and then it's sort of propping up that
reputation that i want to have
but if i do that it keeps me from the
process of discovering something
that happens in that proc like a nice
experience i think of
just like documenting over creating or
rehearsing or
thinking in public it's um there's just
something about
this energy of being seen in the mode of
discovery
that i want more of in my life and then
those are also
i could look at that in the terms of
freestyle like i know when someone is
truly in that essence of freestyle and i
almost want another name for it because
freestyle like in hip-hop culture comes
from a written
that's just free of style so it's just
like a bunch of bars it might not tell a
story it's sort of just random
the freestyle and then like in the
essence i'm speaking of it is sort of a
stream of consciousness and it doesn't
even have to be
hip-hop or rap it could be
conversational but it just has a little
more of that music and that
that rhythm and poetry in it so i'm
interested in calling other things like
streaming or
i'm searching a little bit there um and
then
yeah the same as the the freestyle
artists that i've been most attracted to
i can make that same connection to like
journalists
right so if i can see a journalist in
like that true authentic space
of discovery and they're sharing that
that process
rather than like perfecting everything
before it's shared
yeah i like that that's what i'm leaning
towards right now
yeah yeah i like that a lot and like the
thing that
that i think is the closest that i'm
doing well like i feel like i'm living
my whole life like that right now in a
way
uh just following the damon and whatnot
but like my journals every morning i
write and just almost feel like they're
channeled i'm pushing myself at the edge
of my thinking
they're all different qualities colors
but all these emotions are being fleshed
out of them too
and it's like and there's a part of me
that just wants to like
hit a home run each time and so i'm like
oh what was the one that got the most
attention or which one that felt really
good and try to replicate that when i
i even attempted it i can't attempt it
because it's just so inauthentic
um and it's the same thing with with
that match with
freestyling um what do you say there's a
process of it becoming more natural to
get into that space where it felt like
you were channeling or streaming your
consciousness or is it like
equally challenging to get there every
time how is your relationship with that
sort of sweet spot
um unfolded i would say like 90
over 90 percent of time it's it's easy
it just just i fall into it
um these days because
i'm not really thinking i'm just like
listening these days uh with every
aspect of my life
uh some days i feel really sluggish and
then there's like a challenge and i'm
like
pumping back espresso after espresso
just to get something going
um and it feels a little forced those
days but
yeah i think it's just i don't want to
speak too much of it because it's like
you know
i could lose it tomorrow type thing but
i i think i'm getting uh
like you know you get a felt sense of
the the process in a way
um and
what came up too is that i like
as you know one of my projects here it's
almost like a bait and switch this whole
stova project because it's like there's
only like two real stoics like me and
daniel
in this whole kind of like community
that's forming and then everyone else is
like not really a stoic in this space
um but i really want to reinvent
stoicism i want it to be reborn
and because it's like it's a like the
majority of the text went just
went missing throughout history no one
really knows how they practiced we just
got these core pro
like um propositions that just like
any self-help author would agree with
too so it's not like magic or anything
sure so why not make it sexy you know
like why not like
have these cultural practices like
freestyle and purpose it in order to uh
become a sovereign individual you know
so the socialism
it's like focus on what's in your
control not and what's not in your
control is
uh um what someone thinks of you you
know what your
avatar in the spectacle looks like to
someone else you don't have control over
that
but you have control over what you say
in this moment and how you say it
and a practice a psychotechnology like
freestyling if you
repurpose it with that philosophical
lens it helps so much
becoming a better stoic it helps so much
becoming a better philosopher
a better sense maker you know you name
it
yeah one way it's helped me a lot is by
getting that opportunity in those
moments where i say something that i
feel embarrassed by
or i make a mistake or i'm just not
quite
hitting the target the way that i want
like the words just aren't adding up the
way that i imagine them to
um there's so many things that come up
where i feel
um like i'm i'm kind of i'm missing
yeah and especially the embarrassment or
the awkwardness or like just like
looking like i'm fumbling
and in those times to just send myself
some love
and then do it again yeah and like
having that practice that really
encourages just like
whatever my last effort was just like
forgetting about it entirely
and then jumping in again and so in that
way it's like
it can be very unforgiving in the moment
because
i'm i don't feel like i'm in control of
it
and so it's going to almost take me
where it's going to take me
but then forgiving in the sense that
like as soon as i enter this freestyle i
forget what the embarrassing thing was
that happened in the last one in a way
i'm just
boom i'm here in a new in a new moment
and so that's a way that it has been a
real practice and
i'm interested in this conversation
because i'm also
i'm wanting to reframe this as a as a
practice
and it sort of is a a new thing many
people have
practiced freestyle done freestyle and
say traditional hip-hop ciphers
or in a performative way though
this experience of like using freestyle
very intentionally as
like as a life practice for inner
development
yes that sort of happened in me very
organically no one taught me really how
to do that i just that was like my
process of discovering it
yeah yeah that's what i was gonna ask
you like like uh so freestyling as a
psychotechnology that's not a thing
yeah yeah i mean i think it is in the
sense that like
when someone's freestyling whether
they're using it in that way
intentionally or not
it's a psycho technology like right
right and there have been so many people
like this is
hip-hop there's an entire scene of
hip-hop that was not people that were
recording artists they would just go to
clubs and freestyle just
cipher it's a whole world it's a whole
culture
and so it's been being used and i think
in a very
like powerful way to connect communities
and to empower individuals and
communities
and to keep it's like to
freestyle and and hip-hop was a practice
for individuals in
certain um neighborhoods and cultures
and
um parts of i mean especially in its
birth in in new york and it's unfolding
there it's like
this people had to do hip-hop and engage
in cyphers to like keep a personality
going
because there were so many um forces
that wanted to
make them feel suppressed and so this
was like a tool to rebel
and for me i was the quiet shy kid
sitting at the table so like
sure i didn't grow up like someone in
that was um
in a poor community somewhere in new
york i grew up in like the suburbs
super sheltered but still in my own way
i was disconnected from like my voice
and like my
expression and so freestyle kind of
found me at a time where it could be a
tool
for me to develop a character
and personality and a voice so i think
that it has been used for that it's been
a it's been a
seen by a lot of people as as a very
powerful like tool
um and something that has quite
literally like saved lives
and built communities and like kept
people together
so there's something about all that
that's important to me like i want to
give respect to where
this thing came from
yeah there's like a history
socio-economic history about it that did
serve
a psycho-technology function
but my sense is that it never really had
that conscious frame
that this is a psychotechnology uh life
practice
and then that's something especially
tied to the whole sense making
stoicism philosophizing type thing that
seems somewhat
new or a new spin on it that you're
doing and who knows maybe there's
someone in japan doing exactly the same
thing that we don't know about or
whatever
um yeah i like that a lot
it's a tool for going meta as well
because what i find is like the best way
to practice freestyle is to just
freestyle about
what is happening right now in this in
the center of this freestyle
so if i'm freestyling with you and i
might be searching for all kinds of
profound ideas that i could share so
that you'd be impressed
or i can freestyle about what i noticed
and then from there by sharing what i
notice then imaginations will come up so
then i should freestyle about what i
imagine
great now what do you notice about what
you're feeling about that imagination
and so it's really dialing into that
as like a stream of consciousness and uh
sort of observing what is here now
rather than like the performative
element
where it's like you know people would
sit in their rooms and like write
bars and kind of meditated on it and
practice and then they show up at the
club and sort of
show off so there's still a freestyle
element to it
um but i think where i'm directing this
is
in that in that um sort of investigative
stream of consciousness
yeah yeah it's an interesting challenge
because it's like
there's a couple of challenges that i
want to talk to you about with this
thing
um so one one is interesting about the
actual psychotechnology there
is that you're right in order to make it
pure if you will or
good or however whatever qualifier you
want to put on that is um
you got to be in the moment you can't be
in performance mode you got to be in
being mode like as
raviki calls it but the thing is if
you're
being mode in in it's evident to other
people then you're being mode
and then it's sort of like people want
to applaud you right it's almost like
it's an excellent performance
it's like you can't avoid the um
sort of uh being in the spectacle
because the spectacle is going to notice
or people going to notice via the
spectacle in a way
and then it's so hard not to get seduced
by that because it's like i remember
improv when i took improv i just took
improv
uh acting for just to get confident in
uh social situations so i can kind of
speak extemporaneously and just
not try to engineer words and stuff and
it worked but i find
improv especially sketchy improv it's
like everyone gets addicted to like
saying stupid stuff so they get claps
laughs right and so then and then people
i noticed in the improv community and
anyone was in improv you know uh i'm not
gonna apologize i think it's true so
it's like
it's like people like in the improv
community that i hung out with i
couldn't really stand hanging out with
them because
they're always making jokes all the time
and as they're like they're competing
each other with making jokes they're
trying to
joke each other and i'm like can we just
like i like jokes but can we just talk
serious for like
a couple seconds um and so i didn't like
the
improv community but i think they were
trained for that
because they got the applause and i
imagine there's something similar to the
like what's the cipher i don't know what
that that term is like so the cipher is
basically a group of people
circled up and playing beats and then
taking turns
spinning bars freestyling okay so i
imagine these ciphers or these
sessions that you have it's like you
have to be in that flow state that being
state but then you're getting recognized
because if you're dropping like you know
hot bars or whatever you guys call it
it's like it's like yes
more of that so you're almost trained to
be to be a certain way
now one thing that's really interesting
about that is that if you if someone
stepped into a cipher or showed up at a
club
and they were they used another bar that
someone else
spit or they even mimicked someone
else's flow
people were in there like it was they
took it a very serious responsibility to
make sure that you were not near
mirroring anybody so it was almost like
this
um outside force that like kept people
navigating towards something that was um
i want to say unique or it's like kind
of
yeah pushing them more into that space
of like what is going to be the
expression that is like that's
the flow that emerged from you and of
course it's going to be influenced by
others that we hear
there's something about that there was
this cultural force that kept people
from copying and mimicking others
and instead discovering like their
personality their flow
yes it sounds like the psycho technology
already existed
it's just it wasn't uh thought about
as like a practice that can be fit into
an ecology of practices like we're
having at the stove the wisdom gym or
whatever
um and what's interesting that's very
fascinating because hip hop was birthed
out of an idea of
um art and graffiti
um like b-boying dancing and
rap so it was hip-hop as like when in
its
um origin was this ecology of practices
in a sort yeah it was this combination
of these
these three things um but yeah it's very
different it's like i i feel like i'm
now
um borrowing that
practice and then yeah repurposing it
for this new sort of movement
yeah totally and so the thing i find
challenging about
um like maybe marketing it or getting
people to come
is uh first there's this
it's an artistic expert expectation
right it's like i'm not a good freestyle
rapper
i've never done this before why should i
even try doing this
right um so that's one thing
it's like the intimidation factor even
like signing up
and then when you go in it's like me
camille like camille did one i did one
of my wife uh we did it different times
and we want to come back
it's just that like it though the last
last couple weeks have been really busy
but i probably could have made time but
i'm like i don't really want to put
myself through that again right now
i really want to like put myself in a
nice edge and like feel all that cringe
and everything
um i have to really build up to it and
even though i have the capacity to do it
it's still
i'm hesitant and if i'm hesitant there's
going to be tons of people that are
hesitant to it
so i guess how do you get people like
that that's a marketing question that
we're probably both at the edge of our
thinking with is how do you get people
into the space and risk feeling the
cringe looking stupid
all that stuff because it's one thing if
you have a history of freestyle then
it's like
i remember there's a couple people that
came through sessions that they were
like experts and almost felt like they
were showing off and everyone was
stumbling around type thing
it's like they weren't after their
knife's edge um
so yeah what was your thoughts on that
yeah
so i think framing as the
focusing on the result or the the
intention of what is going like
what are we going to become by doing
this which is
um deepening our relationship with
uncertainty
or freestyling through unknowingness or
uh overcoming perfectionism and
self-doubt things like this
rather than like framing it as freestyle
it's you know because people might be
like i've never freestyled before
but i do want a deeper relationship with
uncertainty or i do want to
deepen my trust in myself or whatever it
is so i think from a marketing
perspective definitely
focusing on the the result rather than
the mechanism that gets the result
yeah and then
and then finally for me i think now part
of what's at the
the edge of my thinking is and
nick's session gave me new ways to think
about this um concept unfolding is what
is the concept that i can create to
describe this thing that we're doing
because it is different
than freestyle in the traditional
hip-hop sense of the word
when people start i don't encourage them
to like
try and show off and have fire bars and
like make the whole crowd go like ooh
like what i want is for people to
actually just speak
conversationally in a way where they're
streaming their consciousness in the
moment they're not thinking about what
they're going to say but they're
letting what comes up come out it's this
honest
self-discovery in the moment but the
beat
in the music it is there as like a as a
lubricant it
gives that sense of rhythm yeah that
allows for a flow to happen
because if i just ask someone to just
speak uh it's a different experience if
i just were to stream my consciousness
conversationally
without the music the music adds this so
good
sort of this yeah this background this
foundational
thing and then what happens from there
is that that musicality that rhythm
it will start to as i get a momentum
then i might start to actually change my
flow i might to become a bit more
musical i might start to rhyme
and then it just allows for it to
escalate uh to a place that is
that allows for
like a deeper engagement there's music
to me i don't i've not even begun to
really understand
how uh powerful like engaging in music
is but i just
look at it it's freaking music man so i
look at like improvisational jazz and
all of these
things and then i look at what's
happening in these conversations around
dialogues dialectic
some stuff that john and and chris are
working on
and how i yearn to be in i love being in
that space of that spontaneous
discovery and that being in the magic in
the middle as riyavek calls it
right and so and then i i connect it
with music i connect that with like
being um
like improv jazz or the grateful dead
and these
these movements that happen through
through
through music and i just i want to
participate in music as well
so it kind of bridges those worlds for
me it's like so i guess if someone
is really interested in dialogues and
they also want to be more musical then
this is like the perfect
place for them to come and explore that
okay let's just get some ideas um
so what did i what did i want to say um
yeah just uh just there just give me one
moment yeah yeah
so there's something i wanted to say it
was like it was like burning but it's
just sort of like it's hiding right now
um the one thing i would say is like uh
i have a desire to kind of figure out
the
the correct phrase for this thing
like so you mentioned nick benjamin who
um he comes to a lot of your ciphers and
the freestyling
and uh he did a session at the store
called concept unfolding
where we're in this kind of liminal
state we need to kind of create
concepts to help ground us we can't just
rely on galaxy brains like
the board from them we got to create our
own and we can have that capacity so he
created a psychotechnology for that
and um yeah it's interesting with the
freestyle because
it's like you're borrowing uh an
existing thing an existing culture that
has an existing reputation
and it's like we're trying to attract
people to play
with that but that's going to be
intimidating for people who are not only
who are like not already super users in
it um
and then your purpose is different sort
of like think about improv
though the two things came back to me
now the thing about improv was the
sketch improv is like
such a beautiful skill set uh and travis
man
our friend he used to work for second
city and they actually had
a thing where they purposed improv in
order for business insights
but the sketch improv it was like it it
was catered towards the the the jokes
and then the laughs
right the same thing with uh i guess i
imagine the freestyle community that
what's rewarded there is what you called
uh
hot bars or yeah you want to be
dope yeah yeah and so it's like you you
want to like
you're you're training yourself to get
that and you see this
line and it was like oh man you know and
um
but when i did your uh freestyle for the
pandemic session
it was more like just the fact that
you're spitting something out right it's
like there's a love there
uh so you're rewarding something
different with your psychotechnology
you're rewarding that flow um another
thing
i want to be judged for my willingness
to like go all in
not for how technically skillful it was
yeah and so it's like um even the kind
of the freestyle itself
is almost like it's like biased towards
that
getting reward for the hot bars or
whatever and so that
that that insight right there might help
us with the concept unfolding to kind of
put a concept there that kind of like
maps over to it
the other thing too that came up was um
dale carnegie so i'm like a trainer dale
carnegie and dale carnegie
the corporation's been around for over a
hundred years uh he wrote the book i
went friends of influence people
he was an actor right and he he he
couldn't make it as an actor
and so i don't know if you couldn't make
it as an actor but he had an acting
background
it didn't work for him or something and
then he started teaching public speaking
uh courses at the ymca using his acting
skills
right and then that that evolved there
so it's like the bait and switch is
about public speaking improving yourself
but use acting techniques the course is
still going on today
i have an acting background so when i
took it originally i'm like i know what
he's doing here
right but most people who take it
they're not they don't even think acting
they just think okay i'm just acting
stupid in order to be more confident to
get over my social anxiety
so i could be more myself um so the bait
and switch there
could be happen in this thing too it's
like you're using the freestyle
technology
but it's not marketed as freestyling
it's market as public speaking this or
that
how to win friends and influence people
or whatever yeah and the last thing i'll
say there that came alive
uh was out of all the sort of the
community sessions that we have with the
stone our wisdoms in
so far the one where i felt most
communitas was your session
when we're all flowing together with
that beat i felt a oneness there and i'm
like this
is it i got a taste of it you know i've
tasted it in other areas of my life
in person circling sessions what not but
i really got a taste of it
on zoom with you guys and so this is why
i'm kind of annoyed
because uh maybe you're averaging what
10 people per session because it's like
there's a struggle kind of getting
people into his other sessions are
having like 60 people
the majority have like you know 20 to
30. and like how can we get more people
in the session
um because i've tasted it and i see the
potential of it
and i want people to experience it i
want people to experience your gift
yeah yes thank you thank you for sharing
that
um i very interesting for me because
again i've been to i've done about a
dozen
retreats in the united states canada
costa rica hawaii
all based around connecting groups of
people the whole purpose is for people
to show up as solo travelers
and leave with like 50 new awesome
friends that was the idea
and for me consistently where i felt the
most group flow was
always the musical jam sessions around
the fire every time
like every every retreat my peak
experience happened
in a musical jam session and so
i just really connect with it as a
as a necessary ingredient for communitas
like i just for me
in my community that because i see
myself living
whether it's in a a shared neighborhood
or some type of
emergent commune format i see myself
living
in communitas and i would like to be
able to go and
make music around the campfire any night
that i wish
and so and it's not
and yeah i mean i think there is a way
for me to dial this in because
i am not musically talented i haven't
there's nothing in me that should like
say that i'm like good or i'm i'm uh
in any way yeah like uniquely qualified
to be able to do this
so yeah i mean i'm just i'm with you i
would like more people to experience
this because
i think that it's a i think it's a
really
like important ingredient and
i've experienced group flow and it's in
its own
moments in multiple sessions at the
stowa
though consistently in these freestyle
ciphers there's a different
quality where it is really
that is what we're that's the purpose in
a sense like
that's where we're aiming toward is that
experience of group flow
and so that's what i want to keep doing
and i'm grateful for these sessions
being like
has as they've been like having 10
people there i know there's a there's
one person that's been to every one so
far i think which i really appreciate
and um but yeah even in these like small
groups of 10 i've been able
to really experiment and have some
really
amazing experiences that i think will
help inform these
bigger groups and as it grows so i think
it's important for me to like remember
to be grateful for this
sort of smaller more intimate setting
right now but i'm also looking toward
like okay
i want to get more people feeling this
yeah yeah totally it's like
if you're not operating out of ego then
you're going at the right pace usually
um and uh it's like there's no failure
only feedback
and this is still a project is is
growing slowly and it needs to grow
slowly but there's also like
an urgency too because we're faced with
a medic crisis and i think most people
in space know that the communitas is the
answer
for this um and so with this session i
think like
step well i think you're right uh
marketing it and even the title has to
gesture towards
more of what you're trying to achieve
like
with like the flow and whatnot
communitos rather than
the actual sort of uh um the
performance piece of it yeah and also
because the modality changes like that's
what i'm realizing like freestyle is
the actual what it is and how i
facilitate it and how i use it that it's
changing and so i don't want it to be
and then also i want it to have a new
a new name and so i'm calling on my
coinage game here and yours and anyone
else
yeah so yeah it's like the modality can
can change and evolve
so it really is about what's like where
are we aiming yeah yeah so
i like that let's just like with the
quinnish game i just wrote three things
uh
to myself where it's like free logos so
like dialogues like free logos
uh uncertainty rhythm unknowing flow or
knowing this flow
uh like i'm not too crazy about any of
those but it's just like
something that isn't that spirit
yes absolutely i'm with you yeah because
if we have like a kind of a name where
it's like uncertainty rhythm or
annoyingness flow what the heck is that
and but it makes it they know what it
means
because it makes sense it's like okay
you're flowing with unknowingness you're
flowing with uncertainty or something
like that
and then if you have a nice tight copy
and maybe like a video preview
of it i think we can get this some
people here
well flowing with unknowingness is a
double double bar rhymes twice flowing
with unknowingness
i like that yeah that's good
yeah uh what's your sense to rename it
to that flowing with annoyingness
i like that good multi-syllabic bar
um yeah that's i i really like that and
that's flowing with unknowingness that's
i like that it's i'm flowing
with unknowingness i want it to be it's
like it's about relationship it's about
relationship to this
to this unknowingness to this
uncertainty that's how i see it i'm good
with that
yes so i'm gonna i'm gonna change it uh
maybe you can send me some copy
uh cool yes and the page or beat up page
or whatever the website
and then let's change some copy and then
i'll just change the the thing and then
uh travis is going to
um market your event raven's events
socratic speed dating
and another one uh because i think those
ones would be good to
oh the stoic breath the wim hof uh
repurposing
um because i think those ones would be a
good entry points to the store
and i just love the fact man just like
taking these cultural artifacts like
freestyling
which emerged in order almost like an
ecology of practice
merged as an act of rebellion to a
pathological culture
right yeah and it did so in an
unconscious like organic beautiful
fashion
and art came from that that's how art
comes about but now
it's like you know us meta people where
we cannot not be conscious of what we're
doing because we're always going
to the middle there
so we can kind of repurpose some of
these beautiful practices and
and help them uh or
let them help us get communitos yep
yeah that's so good because that's how i
feel about freestyle i'll literally pray
i'm like
use me in the in the right way like
let me be an instrument um
that's it it's because i have found
myself so many times tempted to like
want to position myself as this thing
and like and kind of
form it to my intention and it's like
ooh even as i
embody that i'm like no like it's every
time that i've really
surrendered to this expression things
are created that are some that are
much more rich than what i
conjured up and what i thought it was
going to be and so like that's what i
want to
keep letting it take me is yeah toward
that rich experience of
of communitas and and being with the
music i want to i want to be
i want to experience the music of the
music of life
and this is just one way that really is
is helping me do that
yeah man yeah and something just came up
it's like
you were at the store since the
beginning so we've been here for two
months now and you've been pretty much
here since the beginning
and i always got a good sense about you
right away it's like oh this guy has a
good soul
right it was like it's evident to me
like i sniffed it out right away
and same thing with your lady raya right
who does the currently doing the
oxytocian party
like you guys are just like man
like how these people exist it's like so
pure and innocent and innocent's the
wrong word but it's like
i think reya called you a new soul uh
when i was talking to her like it's like
like there's like something yeah that's
an interesting one to me i've had people
tell me things like i'm a volunteer soul
which means
i didn't have to come to earth but i did
and i don't i don't believe these things
but it is it is a little bit weird for
me to notice
patterns i'm like yeah how are these
people that are in totally different
memetic tribes they don't know each
other
or really communicate they'll say
different things about me i don't know
how to relate to it because it doesn't
like land on me is like yeah that's it i
am a volunteer soul
or like i am a new soul but it's just
interesting i've um
yeah so so what do you think it is
what's
oh my goodness i don't know it feels
weird for me to theorize about it like i
just feel like
you know shy and like i don't know i
feel like i just feel like this is like
a really normal guy
like um
i don't know i feel really lucky like i
feel like really the right
influences for me i just i found
really at the right time i was in a
ripe space in my life for transition
coming out of high school
um which i didn't finish i never
graduated high school and so i was in
this space of like
i had two po i just not even two i had
these all these possible paths
and i just right at the right time the
right books
the right youtube videos all the right
things that like
reoriented me happen and so maybe i was
some of these things before all of that
but uh
i don't know man it's weird for me
because i noticed patterns and how
others describe me it's and then i'm
like
i don't know i just don't know what to
make of it sometimes
my read is that i'm very sensitive to uh
like power dynamics
like that chimpanzee politics stuff like
i can tell when someone is doing
some sort of machination in order to get
a higher status level
uh or trying to get more like climb the
dominance higher here the prestige
hierarchy
in a certain interaction and i don't get
that sense from you
uh right like so it's like there's no
like like
like i don't see you threatening people
let's just put that one in a social
interaction it's like oh tyson
let's just flow together it's not like
ooh tyson is
trying to you know like beat his chest
in a certain way even though you do have
that that
and almost like like i said there's like
a masculinity in your voice when we're
at the
the last collective presenting session
like both you and me like our thumbs
both came activated at the same time it
seems like right
so uh does that land for you yeah that
definitely lands
i don't think i really ever had much of
an opportunity to like get momentum in
that game
which i'm grateful for yeah yeah in that
game of um
like rivalrous games and trying to like
one-up people and get on top of others
or
bring others down so i could feel like i
was higher i didn't i just uh
for one reason or another i just never
went that way and so i don't have much
experience in it so if i tried to do
that i don't even think i'd be that good
at it
yeah it's like i always have trouble
pronouncing that word but non-rivalrous
yeah non-rivalrous
you know games or game b kind of stays
like almost you're you're a natural fit
for it in a way
sure yeah yeah it feels like a
natural fit for me where this is all
going in this um
yeah i think that i have an inclination
toward play
yeah like wanting to to play over
perform
and yeah like when i'm sometimes i feel
most myself
when i'm with like uh my little baby
cousin
and things like that um
yeah so and then at the same time i'm
like i have these parts of me that are
um waking up that are much more
like directed and can be aggressive and
can get
angry and want to fight and
those are new but what's interesting is
i feel like they are
awakening in the right type of container
that i would want them to awaken
in like toward a mission where it's like
oh yeah this is like
this is good like if i'm gonna learn how
to um turn on these parts of me that
want to
to fight and defeat old
certain paradigms or ideas it's like i
feel like i have a good container to
channel that rather than like
um i don't know in a boardroom or
something yeah yeah it's this way like
like when i'm writing crazy in my
journal like stealing the culture or
whatever
like you text me like you have my sword
sir
okay cool let's just bring the sumos
yeah i was also watching lord of the
rings and like
that scene where you have a dwarf and an
elf
and men and hobbits and a wizard and
they're like
you have my sword and my axe like that
always stuck with me it's like this is
epic and now here we are mediating
mimetic tribes
right so we've got dwarves and elves and
men all coming together
and so yeah you'd said something that
there's this energy of like when you
declare certain missions and like
direction
for this embodied tribe um
it's i appreciate that like i i feel
because i look into like the world of
people i've been associated with and
some of them like their mission is like
stop bill gates
or some of them their mission is to um
just like
spread love and light or something like
they have all these missions and like
declared objectives
and or in the past there's a lot of like
just entrepreneurs like they're just
about like building a business and like
taking care of me and mine
yeah and so they caught me at different
times in my life where i was like
appreciating something about them
um but there's just something here that
i've found in
sessions at the stoa in your letters in
conversations with friends that i've
been meeting lately
around this um emergent game b
and that is identifying like a more
something that is just that feels more
right as a as a mission or a direction
or aims
and so i think that there's something
about when you have the
when you actually ain't like name some
of those things i feel like this trust
in you that
these are uh like at least good
directions to aim the collective arrow
or the ship
that we're all a part of um and so then
i felt yeah that inspiration to let you
know
like if you're if you name a mission
that is important
like in a way that i can serve with my
sword which might be my words and
freestyle
like um i'm there it's awesome
um i have a
couple questions with that um but our
hour is almost up
uh you cool to stay five minutes after
do you have to balance
no i'm good okay cool yeah so the um
because you were here since the
beginning of the story like kind of like
any thoughts on how
you s see it evolving so far and where
do you think it's
going um
so i'm especially
resonant with in-person events and live
experiences
that teach a bunch of people tools for
developing communitas
and an ecology of practices and then
those people
building their own more like long-term
permanent
communities and then having something
like the stoa which is like the place
that all of these networks of
communities then we can gather and
cohere
in this virtual setting and engage in
practices
share what we're learning engage in
dialogue that keeps us
connected as embodied tribes around the
globe
so that we can keep learning from each
other and not be like disconnected in
our own
little bubble but growing together
and then having like live experiences
where then members of all these embodied
tribes can gather in one place
and meet and share and connect yeah so
it's like a central space for
this network of embodied tribes yeah man
and so it's like my plan before this
whole thing was to open up a
philosophical coffee shop
and i feel like it was like all doing
like you know
a year or two but now if we ever if
covet ever goes away
i'm i'm doing it now you know like i'm
ready for it
and but i still think you can operate in
two economies like the market economy
where it's like a coffee shop but then
the sort of gift economy the spiritual
space
and this is the connective one the one
that you're saying
and it's kind of cool because this this
i would never predicted a freestyling
event uh what are we calling it now
again like i wanna i'm gonna call this
uh flowing with unknowingness flowing
with another i'm gonna call it episode
that flowing which i'm gonna write it
down without knowing this
um so this i didn't know that flowing
with annoying this session uh was going
to happen here but i'm so glad it did
and it feels so so right
and so it's like a natural ecology of
practices emerging what we're dub in the
wisdom gym
and i'm an adjunct researcher of the
consciousness wisdom studies lab at the
university of toronto with john vervicky
so the idea is is to do genuine research
scientific research
on this and maybe we can have a meta
understanding of how to engender
like this is like a why shaman and
gender in ecology of practices
so everyone can do their own version of
it it's not the exact same thing
because maybe maybe like raven gets into
communitas with asking deep liminal
questions
you know maybe you get intimidated with
freestyle maybe daniel is in some other
way
um so maybe there's multiple ways but
maybe
we can find like this meta framework in
order for it to happen
uh that's awesome and i'm not gonna say
the word but it's delicious
so i i had to say it i had to say it um
and yeah so imagine there's some kind of
like
in-person communities maybe it's not a
coffee shop maybe it's just like a
retreat
that like you're suggesting and then
they have this sort of like
connected with uh um this kind of online
digital space
and because the age of medic tribes has
to be over i mean it has that that has
to be done with
because that's not going to get us
anywhere yeah and it's so it's so
difficult to like
actually belong to any of them because
the second i belong to one and i start
to think my
for myself when i publicly ask a
question then i'm
a normie now and or i'm a sheep and like
i'm out
so now where do i belong i gotta go jump
on another bandwagon and that's what i
kind of how i see it as like bandwagon
hopping yeah
and i think like uh yeah maybe i
shouldn't say this but uh
maybe i'll say it anyways uh it's uh
like just like
i wanted to be sort of like a we're like
the cool kids you know what i mean like
in like in the cafeteria like oh
these like what the what the heck are
they doing what are they talking about
what's communitas what's the stoa
you're like yeah i kind of want to be a
little bit obscure but not obscure
enough where it's too intimidating or
anything
um because i want to like like what
raven says it's seduce the culture
and you're not going to seduce it if
you're not attractive that's good we
should want to be the cool kids i mean
and i look at myself
like you know 17 years old
up for grabs i am really grateful
that the people that i chose to go and
involve myself with they looked really
damn cool on the internet
yeah they're making youtube videos
traveling the world looking good they're
fit they're having fun they're laughing
having they had a great lifestyle and i
was attracted to it and then i went to
one of their events
i learned about radical honesty then
boom boom boom
so i'm really glad that they looked at
and some people would call them out
for being cocky or thinking too highly
of themselves and they were just like
whatever like we're
we're doing what we like and so i'm
really glad that they
allowed themselves to you know want to
be the cool kids and so it's the same
thing
um i think there's something about that
that is definitely
yeah it's the i think it's the
aesthetics and i'm attracted to
even like if i'm gonna if i'm looking
for a book and i'm in that receptive
state
space of wanting to get a book i'm gonna
look for one where the the cover and the
art
calls to me same yeah and it's like you
know
it feels good looking good it just does
like when you're when you're when you
have a stressor working out for a while
and you're looking look in the mirror
and like man i'm looking awesome it just
makes you want to work out more
like when i was talking to colin it's
like i want to look good naked
and he says yeah like i want to look
good dancing i want to look good naked
i'm like yeah why not because it just
makes you feel good
but the whole idea is not to get seduced
by the spectacle and then the
impressions that it creates it's sort of
like
the feeling be looking beautiful in
genders a
and try to like repurpose that towards
the communitas
towards you know this this juicy
spiritualness that we were aiming for
yeah yeah i mean there was a time where
i felt like i would spend so much time
obsessing with things about like the way
that i looked whether it was my hair or
like my skin
and acne and all these things and a lot
of my creativity and attention
just went toward how i looked and so it
feels good to get to a place where i'm
like where
and i'm working on this right now with
actually my body and my physical fitness
so that it's like my body looks a type
of way where i'm just like oh yeah i
feel good about it
and all of a sudden there's like almost
like just like a freedom
uh it's like my creativity starts to
then move elsewhere i'm not concerned
about if i look um
strong or attractive because i believe
it to be true
and i know some people that will just
sort of like will themselves into
believing it just
purely through their thoughts which has
its own things like self-love no matter
how you look like good respect
though for me like i don't i don't want
that i want to like really look at
myself be like i look awesome
on to the next thing now i don't have to
think about it like i'll just keep
you know keep working out and moving but
it's not consuming my
creativity or my attention yeah yeah and
that going back to the law of attraction
thing it's like
like you know just kind of willing your
belief on something yeah
yeah but if you're like willing uh
something that's like doesn't correspond
to reality whatsoever
right then you're just eluding yourself
yeah
cool man um so anything else you think
uh
we should touch on or jam on or do you
have any final thoughts
um i want to one thing i wanted to
connect back to your question that sent
us
in down all this was about like where
the stow was going
and i was also wanting to call in
because there's the wisdom gym and the
psychology of practices
then there's also the tenant of the
sense making
that is happening so like having jordan
hall on for example
and it's like jordan hall is a type of
person that
has this view of the world that then
when like representatives from all the
embodied tribes come on to the sense
making
call like they can learn about how they
can be more usefully
um mobilized toward creating a better
word
world for the whole so there's something
about that as well like that sense
making node
that sort of informs like here now where
this embodied tribe
we've got this ecology of practices
we're becoming more wise more strong
we have a stronger community and it's
like we're going to have our own
initiatives that
just arise from our creativity but
there's something that i really
uh respect about the um
the those who can
so inform me inform back to me this is
what's
going on where like the world can use
support
these are the challenges that we face as
a collective and it's those are some of
the things that just like
kind of make it more clear how connected
we are as embodied tribes
and how we can like team up with one
another so there's something about that
as well it can be like a place
that i can go and be like okay like our
tribe like we're strong right now
like what can we do like who needs our
help who needs support
totally and uh what i like about sort of
um
i just found myself having this sort of
talent stack of
basically basically kind of my read on
the culture war
being able to speak all these different
perspectives my how to win friends
influence people
with dale carnegie like i can um you
know maybe i'm overreading or i'm
patting myself in the back here too much
but
i feel like i can bring a lot of people
to this digital campfire that would
otherwise not
be in communication with each other um
the idea is to bring them be warm get
them worn by the digital campfire first
one at a time
and see if they can uh have a
communication with each other so this is
like the
our project at the memetic mediation or
the mediation campfire
um and also what you said about like
yeah there's a wisdom gym component
there's like a
psycho technology incubator and if
something works well then you can
report it in the wisdom gym there's also
these like sense making note sessions
like with jordan hall or whatever all
these kind of like really intelligent
people
and i like that that the future dialogue
the dialogue is already happening
is what's different about um the stoa
it's like
almost like a podcast almost like a
lecture but then there's like the
the additional component of the
collective intelligence uh
responding to the the sense making note
and it's almost like it's almost like a
sermon at one point but it's going to be
a reverse sermon
in a way because the sense maker is
going to be influenced by the collective
intelligence
maybe even more so right um because
we're going to gain our discernment
like the the collective presence
psychotech that we're doing every friday
that's just about the question what is
the question that emerges imagine if you
get really skilled at that
yes so there's gonna be a two-way
influence there which is going to be
quite good especially if we can get
all the different kind of chieftains of
all the memetic tribes
playing here so i think there's lots of
lots of potential there
and i'm pretty stoked about it
yeah me too there's something really
juicy about being on a session whether
it's um
with alexander bart or jordan hall
and a question comes up that there you
see them be struck by it
yeah and there's something that is like
uh yeah so juicy about that that i
really appreciate and then it is it's
like well the more that there are these
embodied tribes
developing their skillfulness and
discernment wisdom
coming together on these then the more
skillful we'll get it asking questions
and then the more moved the thinker or
the speaker
giving the sermon that will be by the
questions
and um that's
yeah like that's almost like uh just
something that i'm inspired by is
that feeling in me of
like what is it that i want and of
course there's also this
there's two sides of this but i noticed
something where i really want to ask
a good question and so if there's ever
because i feel like i'm less than or
i'll be left behind if i don't ask a
good question it's like okay i can
notice that
but it's the the longing for me and of
it's the it's the connection that
happens between me and a person when i
ask them a question that like arouses
them
yes yeah i really appreciate that
experience
that's a good heuristic to have like is
this question gonna potentially arouse
and the other person something like
their dame one or whatever
and it's like the whole motto or one
half of the motto of uh
the stoa or the mission is like you know
stealing the culture that was john
vervicky said that and that got prompted
by a question
uh i think it was that was it uh joe joe
asked that question
i didn't ask that question i i didn't
even think of that question
and he might have never came up with
that motto and if kira the dawn he's
apparently doing like a song on it now
right
that would never emerge if someone just
asked a question um
so i'm um yeah i just i love asking the
right question i like the heuristic you
said to arouse something
the other person
cool um so
uh flowing with annoyingness like that
let's let's pitch it
what's when is it when is it happening
great
so yeah flowing with unknowingness is
happening on saturdays
at the stoa 8 o'clock eastern time
and what it is it's an opportunity to
deepen your relationship with
unknowingness so that unknowingness
becomes
less scary and daunting and intimidating
and more
juicy and exciting and it really can be
a
modality for transforming anxiety into
excitement moving from
overthinking and perfectionism to full
engagement and participate participation
that's what it is for me right now and
then i think the cherry on top of all of
that like if we do that as individuals
and we support each other in doing it
then what is created
is this wonderful experience of group
flow
where our relationships become deeper
and then
we are more attuned to the the right
questions to ask
one another and yeah that's like the
cherry on the top is that sweet space of
group flow wow yeah that's good
good pitch i think i'm just gonna cut
that one as a one off and you can use
that as advertisement
all right my friend um i'll stop
recording right now
uh thanks so much for for coming on the
install podcast
yeah thanks so much for having me this
has been a really good time
cool